(Leonard:)Sheldon, we agreed we'd do something
different tonight.
(Sheldon:)All right. Let's go
to the comic book store.
(Raj:)We went to the comic book store
last night.
(Sheldon:)Last night was Wednesday.
Wednesday is comic-book night.
(Sheldon:)We'll be going on Thursday because
it's Anything Can Happen Thursday.
(Leonard:)Way to think outside but pressed right up
against the box, Sheldon.
What are we gonna do tonight?
(Howard:)If I may proffer a suggestion...
(Howard:)...in bars all across this great nation
of ours, Thursday night is Ladies' Night.
(Howard:)As the evening progresses,
we will get better-looking...
...courtesy of 99-cent margaritas
and two-for-one Jell-O shots.
(Leonard:)Come on, Howard, the odds of us picking
up girls in a bar are practically zero.
Oh. Really?
Are you familiar with the Drake equation?
(Sheldon:)The one that estimates the odds
of contact with extraterrestrials...
(Sheldon:)...by calculating the product
of series of fractional values...
...such as stars
with planets likely to develop life?
(Sheldon:)N equals R times FP times NE times FL
times Fl times FC times L?